Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
5582
Kheel Center
80.1 linear ft.
Pamphlets.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The Archives Foreign File is a collection of printed ephemeral documents, issued primarily by foreign and international trade unions and labor organizations. All continents are represented, though the majority of materials is of European origin. Topics covered in this collection include union organizing, unemployment, working conditions, the working class, the labor movement, industrial relations, worker education, international trade unionism, works councils, automation, economic conditions and trends, labor markets, foreign relations, and political movements, including fascism, socialism, and communism. Included in this collection are materials on the World Confederation of Labor and the World Federation of Trade Unions.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into four sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-79
Boxes 80-81 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
Subjects:
Labor unions; Labor unions--Political activity; Labor unions and foreign policy; Labor movement; International labor activities; Working class; Working class--Education; Industrial relations; Labor market; Unemployment; Economic history; Works councils; Work environment; Management--Employee participation; International relations; Labor unions and communism; Labor unions and socialism; Labor unions and fascism; Industrial safety; Industrial hygiene; Communism; Fascism; Socialism; Automation
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other parts of this Collection:
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF)
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1: Boxes 1-22
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2: Boxes 23-44
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4: Boxes 67-79
Boxes 80-82 have not been inventoried at this point.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 45, Folder: 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Internacional de Correos, Telegrafos y Telefonos: Circular Letter No. 36, 1960; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Author: William C. Doherty Jr.
    Format: Publication
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 2: The CLC Pension Plan for workers in small industries // Regime supplementaire de rentes pour les travailleurs des petites entreprises, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress
    Language: English.
  - Item 3: The CLC Pension Plan for workers in small industries // Regime supplementaire de rentes pour les travailleurs des petites entreprises, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Summary statement to the Commission of Inquiry on Unemployment Insurance, 1986; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Author: Dick Martin
  - Item 5: Summary statement to the Commission of Inquiry on Unemployment Insurance, 1986; Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Box: 45, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Donald R. (Don) Montgomery, Secretary-Treasurer, Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Notes: Bio Sketch
  - Item 2: Joe Morris, President, Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Donald R. (Don) Montgomery, Secretary-Treasurer, Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Donald R. (Don) Montgomery, Secretary-Treasurer, Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Julien Major, Executive Vice-President, Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Shirley G. E. Carr, Executive Vice-President, Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Biographical Sketch of Dennis McDermott, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Canadian labour comment, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.6, no.6
  - Item 9: Canadian labour comment, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.6, no.19
  - Item 10: Canadian labour comment, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Canadian labour comment, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Canadian labour comment, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Canadian labour comment, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.6, no.20
  - Item 14: Canadian labour comment, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Canadian labour comment, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Canadian labour comment, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Box: 45, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Fairtytales & fables: about Unions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: UnionsPart of your future, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Box: 45, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Leadership skills instructor manual, 1990; Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Box: 45, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Assessing the memberships attitude toward the Union, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Box: 45, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Consitution, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Consitution, 1982; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Consitution, 1984; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Consitution, 1986; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Consitution, 1986; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Consitution, 1988; Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Box: 45, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1988; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1980; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1976; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1986; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1986; Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Box: 45, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1988; Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1984; Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1978; Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1984; Publication (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Box: 45, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Steward Training, pt. I, Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Notes: workshop material
  - Item 2: Steward Training, pt. II, Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: UnionsPart of your future, Publication (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Box: 45, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: A guide to: Retraining, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Securing your rights: negotiating a closure agreement, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Understanding the process: unions and the adjustment committee, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Digging in: launching a fightback campaign, Publication (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Box: 45, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: More about the Labour College of Canada, 1977; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Notes: flyer
  - Item 2: More about the Labour College of Canada, 1977; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Point of order, Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Author: Canadian Congress of Labour. Research Dept.
  - Item 4: Point of order, Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: The Shop steward: a manual designed to give shop stewards a working knowledge of their duties and responsibilities, Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: The steward//Manual for stewards, Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress. Dept. of Education
  - Item 7: Tech change, 1982; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: The Pension Story, 1980; Publication (Box 45, Folder 11)
    Author: Morden Lazarus
- Box: 45, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Summary of proceedings, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Notes: looseleaf
  - Item 2: Manual on Safety and Health, Publication (Box 45, Folder 12)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress. National Committee on Health and Safety
- Box: 45, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Native Peoples -- Fact Sheet 1, 1976; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress. Social and Community Programs Dept.
  - Item 2: Women in the work force -- Fact Sheet 2, 1977; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Child Care -- Fact Sheet 3, 1975; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Poverty -- Fact Sheet 4, 1977; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Civil Liberties -- Fact Sheet 5, 1975; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: The Environment -- Fact Sheet 6, 1977; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Pollution Control -- Fact Sheet 7, 1977; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Human Rights -- Fact Sheet 8, 1976; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Human Rights Legislation -- Fact Sheet 9, 1976; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: The Handicapped -- Fact Sheet 10, 1975; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Alcoholism -- Fact Sheet 11, 1976; Publication (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Box: 45, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Emmanuel Negassa of Ethiopia attended a CLC Seminar in Nigeria, Publication (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Emmanuel Negassa of Ethiopia attended a CLC Seminar in Nigeria, Publication (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Box: 45, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Notes on Unions 1-8, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Notes on Unions 1-8, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Notes on Unions 1-8, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Notes on Unions 1-8, Publication (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Box: 45, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Staff organizer's white collar manual, 1976; Publication (Box 45, Folder 16)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress. Organization Dept.
  - Item 2: Voluntary white collar organizer's manual, 1976; Publication (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Public relations for unions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Box: 45, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Policy statement approved by the ... CLC constitutional convention., 1970; Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress. Constitutional Convention
  - Item 2: Policy statement approved by the ... CLC constitutional convention., 1974; Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Policy statement approved by the ... CLC constitutional convention., 1975; Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Policy statement approved by the ... CLC constitutional convention., 1976; Publication (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Box: 45, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Departments of the Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress. Education Dept.
  - Item 2: Departments of the Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Departments of the Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Box: 45, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Submission of the B. C. Federation of Labour, Committee on Women's Rights to the Minister of Human Resources on Child Care Requirements, Publication (Box 45, Folder 19)
    Author: British Columbia Federation of Labour (C.C.L.)
  - Item 2: Submission of the B. C. Federation of Labour, Committee on Women's Rights to the Minister of Human Resources on Child Care Requirements, Publication (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Box: 45, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Board of Enquiry Decision under the Ontario Human Rights Code, 1988; Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
    Author: Canadian Labour Relations Board
  - Item 2: In the matters of the Complaints made by Ms. Laurene WiensOntario Human Rights Code, 1980; Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: In the Supreme Court of Ontario Divisional Court, (Reid, Bowlby, Rosenberg JJ), 1987; Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: In the matter of the Ontario Human Rights Code, S.O. 1981, c.53, as amended., 1987; Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: In the matter of the Ontario Human Rights Code, S.O. 1981, c. 53, as Amended between: Ontario Human Rights Commission, 1988; Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: In the matter of the complaint made by Mr. Jim Kennedy dated December 5, 1985, alleging deiscrimination in employment on the basis of handicap by New Liskeard Sheet Metal Works Ltd., 1988; Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: Decision and Order in the matter of the Complaint made by Dashminder Singh Sehdev by his litigation guardian and mother, Ms. Hersharn Kaur Sehdev., 1987; Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: Board of Inquiry Decision under the Ontario Human Rights Code, 1981, c.53, as amended Elaine McAra, Complainant, and Motor Coach Industries and Jeff Constance, 1987; Publication (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Box: 45, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Miscellaneous papers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Box: 45, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Miscellaneous papers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Box: 46, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: CLRB/CCRT Numerical Index, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: CLRB''s Alphabetical Index, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Box: 46, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Subject Index, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
    Notes: pt.1
- Box: 46, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Remedies, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
    Notes: pt.2
- Box: 46, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Bi-Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Box: 46, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Revised pages for the Alphabetical Index to Board Reasons for decision, Publication (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Box: 46, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Multinational Corporations - ITGLWF Policy, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Revised pages for the Alphabetical Index to Board Reasons for decision, Publication (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Box: 46, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Revised pages for the Alphabetical Index to Board Reasons for decision, Publication (Box 46, Folder 7)
    Notes: pt.3
- Box: 46, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Revised pages for the Numerical and Section Index to Board Reasons for decision., Publication (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Box: 46, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Canadian Labour Relations Board -- Revised pages for the Numerical and Section Index to Board Reasons for decision., Publication (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Box: 46, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Labour and social involvement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Emmanuel Negassa of Ethiopia attended a CLC Seminar in Nigeria, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Canadian Labour Congress, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Code of Organizing practices, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Office, Technical and Professional Employees are "With it", Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: More about the Labour College of Canada, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Programme of Business, Peace & Unity, Sixteenth Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Programme of Business, Peace & Unity, Sixteenth Constitutional Convention, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: The CLC Pension Plan for workers in small industries // Regime supplementaire de rentes pour les travailleurs des petites entreprises, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: You're the boss!, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: You are not alone, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Here's the answer, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Welfare Services through union counselling, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: What about international unions, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: UnionsPart of your future, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Welfare is your business!, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Your voice in your community, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Questions and answersabout unions!, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Code of Ethical Practices, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: No flowers by request, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Labour's voice in your province, Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Financial Statement, 1969; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Financial Statement, 1971; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Labour Councils: a manual for guidance in organization and operation of labour councils, 1974; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress. Dept. of Provincial Federations of Labour and Labour Councils
  - Item 25: Tech change: a handbook for negotiations, 1982; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Labour's manifesto for Canada, 1976; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 27: Labour's manifesto for Canada, 1976; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: Labour's manifesto for Canada, 1976; Publication (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Box: 46, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Financial Statement, 1986; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Financial Statement, 1986; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Financial Statement, 1986; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Financial Statement, 1986; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Disposition of matters referred to the Executive Council by the, 1988; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress. Executive Council
  - Item 6: Regulations governing the procedure for the handling of claims for justification and allegations of raiding pursuant to the provisions of the Canadian Labour Congress Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Canadian Labour Congress, Position paper on Canadian jobs strategy, 1987; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Canadian Labour Congress, Position paper on Canadian jobs strategy, Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Submission by the Canadian Labour Congress to the Atomic Energy Control Board on Proposed Revisions to Regulations under the Atomic Energy Control Act (C-83), 1986; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Submission by the Canadian Labour Congress to the Atomic Energy Control Board on Proposed Revisions to Regulations under the Atomic Energy Control Act (C-83), 1986; Publication (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Box: 46, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Canadian Merchant Service Guild, 1975; Publication (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Author: Canadian Merchant Service Guild
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Canadian Merchant Service Guild: Ships Officers Group, 1970; Publication (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Box: 46, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Intercom, 1980; Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
    Author: Canadian Paperworkers Union
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1976; Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1978; Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1978; Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1982; Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1982; Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Item 7: Canadian Paperworkers Union, Publication (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Box: 46, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Bell Canada Communications Sales Employees, 1977; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
    Author: Canadian Telephone Employees' Association
  - Item 2: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Bell Canada Communications Sales Employees, 1979; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Bell Canada Clerical and associated employees, 1981; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Tele-Direct Ltd., Clerical and Associated Employees, 1979; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Bell Canada, Communications Sales Employees, 1982; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Item 6: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Tele-Direct, Clerical and Associated Employees, 1977; Publication (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Box: 46, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Bell Canada, Clerical and Associated Employees, 1979; Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Bell Canada, Clerical and Associated Employees, 1977; Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Tele-Direct, Ltd., Clerical and Associated Employees, 1979; Publication (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Box: 47, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Canadian Postmasters Association, Revenue Postal Operations Group (All Employees), 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Author: Canadian Postmasters Association
  - Item 2: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Canadian Postmasters Association, Revenue Postal Operations Group (All Employees), 1975; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Canadian Postmasters Association, Revenue Postal Operations Group (All Employees), 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreement between the Treasury Board and the Canadian Postmasters Association, Revenue Postal Operations Group (All Employees), 1968; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Box: 47, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1978; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1985; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1981; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Constitution, 1981; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1970; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Bell Canada Clerical and Associated Employees, 1985; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Collective agreement between Canadian Telephone Employees' Association and Bell Canada Communications Sales Employees, 1986; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Box: 47, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A history of organization, 1971; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: A history of organization, 1971; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)